ISAAC WEISS

Auburn, AL (334) 748-1379 weissic@icloud.com

isaacweiss.dev github.com/icweiss22 linkedin.com/in/icweiss22

SKILLS

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ¡Query, knockout.js, DataTables, AJAX
- Languages: C#, C++, Java, Python, Swift, SQL
- Tools: .NET ecosystem. Visual Studio, VS Code, **SSMS**
- Collaboration: GitHub. Teams, Jira, Service Now
- Other: Entity Framework, LINO, Razor

EDUCATION

Auburn University

Samuel Ginn College of Engineering Auburn, AL Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, Business Concentration Minor: French August 2019 - December 2023

GPA: 3.97/4.00 Dean's List (>3.8 GPA) Fall 2019 – December 2023 Awarded Spirit of Auburn Presidential Scholarship – Full Tuition for students with 34 score on ACT (SAT 1500) Awarded ADTRAN Scholarship

(\$1000) for outstanding students in Computer Science

French Club Treasurer

References Upon Request

SUMMARY

Auburn University senior majoring in Computer Science with a Business concentration and a French minor. Very passionate about software engineering, with experience in web development using the .NET ecosystem. Familiar with back-end (SSMS, SQL), middleware (.NET, C#), and front-end (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) tools.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Campus Web Solutions Auburn, AL (May 2021 – December 2022) Full-stack co-op at a web development firm specializing in developing robust web applications for Auburn University.

- Designed, developed, and maintained 30+ of Auburn University's most used web applications using strict coding regulations and security practices, including AU's Vaccine and Pharmacy Scheduler, AU's Board of Trustees Voting System, and AU's Event Ticketing System.
- Leveraged an array of web development tools including HTML, CSS, .NET Framework, ¡Query, C#, Visual Studio, and SSMS to create dynamic and robust digital solutions.
- Assumed mentorship role, providing hands-on learning, conducting live practice sessions, and authoring a comprehensive web development guide to nurture and guide newer co-ops.
- Actively participated in client meetings, effectively communicating technical concepts, and proposing innovative ideas that garnered client approval.
- Implemented agile development methodologies to streamline project workflows, tracking and managing 100+ deliverables with precision using Jira, resulting in timely project completions.
- Prioritized mobile responsiveness, crafting applications that seamlessly adapt across diverse devices. Conducted comprehensive runtime analyses and eliminating performance bottlenecks.
- Led the end-to-end redesign and development initiative for the Auburn University Vice President of Research's site pages (cws.auburn.edu/ovpr). creating a dynamic backend system empowering the client to effortlessly update and manage content.

Exchange Student, Toulon, France (January 2023 – June 2023)

- Immersed deeply in the local culture while honing language proficiency.
- Fostered cross-cultural understanding, building a diverse global perspective.

Hackathon Logistics Coordinator, Auburn, AL (September 2019 – February 2020)

- Managed scheduling, room assignments, vendor communication, and more for months leading up to the event.
- Ensured seamless execution of tasks such as coordinating food services and providing real-time support to participants, contributing to the success of a memorable and impactful Hackathon.

Front Service Clerk, *Publix* Auburn, AL (June 2018 – October 2020)

Efficiently processed customer transactions as cashier and bagger while maintaining a friendly and approachable demeanor.